It's about time for you to die!
Twist!
Envelope!
Twisting Whirlpool-Flowing Water!
My sword's so heavy!
But...
Second Form...
Improved,
Lateral Water Wheel!
EPISODE 10:
TOGETHER FOREVER
I did it!
The Whirlpool move loses force
when it's not underwater!
But thanks to my opponent's attack,
it gained power,
and I was able to envelope the arrows!
Damn!
Curse you! Curse you! Curse you!
All I had to do
was bring back your head,
and I would've won his approval!
I'll never forgive you!
I'll never ever forgive you!
Shoving my face into this vile dirt!
You're going down with me!
Oh no! He's gonna get me!
I'm getting pulled by a force
stronger than the arrows he's hit me with!
I gotta unleash move after move
and go on the defensive,
or my body's going to get smashed!
Fourth Form,
Striking Tide!
The pressure is bearing down on my body,
and I can't swing my sword!
Unleash one!
Unleash a move!
Not here!
Don't let yourself get beat!
Second Form,
Water Wheel!
Waterfall Basin!
Water Surface Slash!
Drop Ripple Thrust-curve!
Whirlpool!
I've never made this
many consecutive moves before!
It feels like both my arms
are about to get torn off!
Nowhere near enough!
More...
Suffer more!
How many more times?
How many?
Don't think about it!
Just keep unleashing moves!
Keep throwing them out!
Not yet!
It's still not enough yet!
Nezuko...
Miss Tamayo...
Yushiro...
I've got a broken rib and leg.
N-No good!
I'm too exhausted to grip my sword!
I gotta get over there!
There's still one more demon!
I'll be there soon!
So be safe, all right?
Please...
be safe!
Ridiculous!
It's child's play for me
to evade a linear attack like this!
Locating you is a breeze, as well!
The same goes for you!
No matter how well
you might conceal yourself,
I can see you clear as day!
What fun this is!
Hey you!
Don't be so rash
just because you're immortal!
Wh-What's wrong?
What do you think you're doing?
Here it comes!
Look at her.
Lady Tamayo...
You little brat!
So, now you can kick
my temari back at me?
How insolent!
You damn brat!
Unbelievable.
Lady Tamayo, is this...
I used a healing serum on her.
Nothing more.
Made exclusively for demons.
It doesn't make one physically stronger.
What we're seeing
is Nezuko's own power.
Without devouring human blood...
Solely on her own...
Nezuko is gaining strength at a rapid rate.
However, her opponent
is also formidable.
If she were to go all-out,
Nezuko wouldn't stand a chance.
I've got to...
do something.
You're an amusing little girl!
This time, I'm going all-out against you!
I wonder how long you can hold out!
Twelve Kizuki demon girl there.
You're in my way!
Step back, you damn fugitive!
Just tell me one thing please.
Are you aware of Kibutsuji's true identity?
What the hell did you say?
That man is nothing but a coward.
He lives in constant fear of something.
Stop it!
Damn you! Stop it!
Do you know why it is
that demons can't band together?
The reason why demons
cannibalize each other?
It's to prevent other demons
from banding together and attacking him.
He manipulates demons to act this way.
Demons like you.
Shut up!
Shut up, shut up!
No way is he that petty!
Lady Tamayo...
is casting a spell.
The power he wields is mind-blowing!
There's no one stronger than him!
Not Lord Kibutsuji!
You've uttered that name
out loud, haven't you?
That will trigger the curse.
Magical Aroma of Daylight.
It weakens its target's brain functions,
rendering that person
unable to lie or keep secrets.
It's immensely potent, Lady Tamayo!
I do feel sorry for you, but...
farewell.
Please forgive me!
I'm begging you! Please!
DEMON SLAYER:
KIMETSU NO YAIBA
Did she just die?
She will die momentarily.
That's the curse.
Her physical body will be destroyed
by Kibutsuji's cells still in her body.
In general,
battles between demons are futile.
It's pointless.
Because they can't inflict
fatal wounds on each other.
Only sunlight and the swords
of the Demon Slayers can do so.
Kibutsuji alone appears
to be able to destroy demon cells.
Don't go inhaling Lady Tamayo's spell!
It's harmful to the human body!
You got that?
Tanjiro...
She is not one of the Twelve Kizuki.
The Twelve Kizuki have numbers
engraved on their eyeballs,
but this demon doesn't have one.
Most likely,
the other demon isn't a member
of the Twelve Kizuki, either.
They're too weak.
Too weak?
At that level?
If Lady Tamayo says so,
there's no mistake.
Still, who knew
there were such stupid demons?
She physically injured Lady Tamayo.
She got exactly what she deserved.
I hope this blood will be instrumental
in developing the healing serum.
I'm going to take care of Nezuko.
Not only did I medicate her,
she also inhaled my spell inadvertently.
I'm so sorry.
Don't move a muscle!
You're on your own now!
I don't want to leave
Lady Tamayo's side!
Not for a second!
DESTROY
Ma... ri...
Mari...
Here's your mari.
Play with me.
You're just like a little kid.
Even though you must've murdered
scores of people.
You were deluded into thinking
you were in the Twelve Kizuki.
Deceived... Compelled to fight...
And now,
you were killed by the Kibutsuji curse.
There's no salvation.
Even after you die,
not even your bones will remain.
Is this the price you pay
for killing others?
Kibutsuji...
This is how that man treats
even those who revere him!
He's a true...
demon!
Miss Tamayo!
Yushiro?
Over here! Over here!
Not that you need to come at all.
But if you want to,
then get down here.
Yushiro!
Only joking!
Hurry down, then, Tanjiro!
Oh, right!
Nezuko!
I moved her to this basement,
where the sunlight won't reach her,
ahead of daybreak.
Nezuko?
Why, you!
Step away from Lady Tamayo!
That's so rude!
Stop it, Yushiro.
I don't mind at all.
Yes, ma'am!
You have such a kind heart,
Lady Tamayo.
You're too beautiful to believe!
Cut... that... out!
Nezuko has been acting in this way
since she awoke.
Do you think she's all right?
There's nothing to worry about.
She's fine.
She probably thinks
you're someone in our family.
Cut it out!
Family?
But I thought the spell
Nezuko is under
causes her to see humans
as her family.
And Yushiro and I are demons.
Cut it out!
But Nezuko has perceived
you two as humans.
That's why she tried to protect you.
At first, I didn't like the idea
of Nezuko being under a spell,
but since it looks like she has
a will of her own, I'm glad that—
I-I'm so sorry! Nezuko!
Nezuko! S-Step away from her!
It's rude, all right?
Thank you...
Nezuko!
Thank you!
Do you still wish to live?
Do you still wish to live
even if you're no longer human?
If this goes on, you will most likely
succumb to your illness.
However,
losing your humanity
will cause you pain and grief.
Do you still wish to live?
Yushiro and I will leave this region.
We've gotten too close to Kibutsuji.
We must conceal our whereabouts soon
or the risk will be too great.
Not to mention, even if I think
I've concealed my identity,
when I interact with humans as a doctor,
people sometimes
see through me as a demon.
The young and the elderly
are particularly perceptive.
Tanjiro...
Yes?
Would you like us to take Nezuko in?
I can't give you an absolute guarantee
that she'll be safe,
but I believe it will be less dangerous
than taking her into battle.
That might be true.
She's right. It would be better
for Nezuko to be in their care.
Miss Tamayo, thank you so much
for your concern.
But...
Nezuko and I are staying together.
We're not going to live
apart from each other.
Never again.
Very well.
In that case, I wish you
long-lasting good fortune in battle.
All right.
We'll be leaving after we erase
all traces of ourselves.
You two get going now!
Right!
Okay, Miss Tamayo, Yushiro,
we wish you well!
Let's go, Nezuko.
Hey!
Don't go rushing off like that!
Tanjiro!
Your kid sister...
is a beauty.
South-southeast! South-southeast!
South-southeast!
Your next location is south-southeast!
I heard you!
I heard, so give me a break
and quiet down!
I'm begging you!
I got the message, so please!
Please!
Please! Please! Please!
Please marry me!
I could die any day, you know!
That's why I want you to marry me!
So please! Please, I'm begging you!
Wh-What's up with that?
What on earth?
PREVIEW
RUSTLE RUSTLE
South-southeast! South-southeast!
I mean, I just fought!
When can I get some sleep?
What? I nailed it?
Not that I was really trying to or anything.
First, it's time for a Taisho secret!
The Demon Slayer Corps' messengers,
the Kasugai Crows, each have a name.
I hear that mine is named
Matsuemon Tennouji.
Okay, one last impression.
"This is your first assignment
as a Demon Hunter!"
Hey! We've been fighting constantly
from the start!
Next, Episode 11, "Tsuzumi Mansion"!
This isn't really the time
for a festival, is it?
TO BE CONTINUED